ANDIRA GITA NAWANGSARI.

Phone +62813-3402-7376 Email: andiragita28@gmail.com ·

LinkedIn Profile: Andira Gita Nawangsari ·

Github: github.com/AndiraGita – andiragita.github.io

A recent graduate from the intelligent system laboratory of Computer Engineering Major, experienced in developing machine learning and data visualization to contribute to research success. An award-winning student researcher that developed a machine learning approach for one of the competitions in GECCO 2021. Motivated to learn, grow and excel in the machine learning and data analytics industry.

EXPERIENCE

MAR 2020 - FEB 2022

STUDENT RESEARCHER, INTELLIGENT SYSTEM LABORATORY, PNU

Preprocessing factory data and using Subgroup Discovery and Genetic Algorithm approach on Python to find the major factors that cause defects in products.

Preprocessing factory data and using Machine Learning and Genetic Algorithm approach on Python to find the combination of features that making the product, which was some sort of coolant engine, to get optimal efficiency and pressure drop.

AUG 2018 - NOV 2018

TEACHING ASSISTANT OF ENTERPRISE SYSTEM CLASS, INFORMATION SYSTEM DEPARTMENT, ITS

Teaching, preparing lessons and providing feedback for the students in Enterprise System Class, which learn about the usage of SAP in the enterprise.

JUL 2018 - AUG 2018

INTERNSHIP STUDENT, TELKOM INDONESIA REGIONAL DIVISION 5

Creating a dashboard with JavaScript and PHP to view the availability of access points in the regional 5 of Telkom Indonesia.

MAR 2017 - JUN 2017

TEACHING ASSISTANT OF WEB-BASED PROGRAMMING CLASS, INFORMATION SYSTEM DEPARTMENT, ITS

Teaching, preparing lessons and providing feedback for the students in Web-Based Programming Class. Mainly teaching about the concept of MVC in website building and the implementation with bootstrap.

MAR 2017 – JUN 2017

TEACHING ASSISTANT OF OPERATING SYSTEMS FOUNDATION CLASS,

INFORMATION SYSTEM DEPARTMENT, ITS

Preparing lessons, and providing feedback for the students in Operating Systems Foundation Class. Mainly helps monitor laboratory work where students learn about the foundation of Windows and Linux operating systems.

EDUCATION

AUG 2019

BACHELOR OF COMPUTER SCIENCE, INSTITUT TEKNOLOGI SEPULUH NOPEMBER,

INDONESIA GPA: 3.75/4.0

Thesis: Sentiment Analysis for Indonesian Language Text On Social Media Using Universal

Language Model Fine-tuning (ULMFIT) Case Study: E-commerce.

MAR 2022

MASTER OF SCIENCE, PUSAN NATIONAL UNIVERSITY, SOUTH KOREA

GPA: 4.44/4.5

Thesis: Optimization of Scheduling Strategies for Dynamic Stacking Problem in Uncertain

Environment

AWARDS

JUN 2021

1st place in Dynamic Stacking Optimization in Uncertain Environments competition held by GECCO (international conference) in 2021

CERTIFICATIONS

AUG 2019

Participant of Digital Talent Scholarship Machine Learning

• OCT 2019

AWS Certified Cloud Practitioner

SKILLS

LANGUAGE

Experienced: Python

Familiar : Java, JavaScript, HTML, PHP

OTHER

Experienced : MySQL, Machine Learning

Familiar : Tableau, Power BI, SAP, MongoDB, Redis, Amazon Web Service (AWS)